JIN KUAN MOO

https://minahhh666.github.io/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/jin-kuan-moo/

Summary

A UCD Computer Science Master proficient in **Chinese Mandarin**, **English**, and **Malay**. **Full stack** development experience in several languages as well as **Agile** methodology. Great networking (**TCP/IP**), OS (**Windows, Linux**) and **machine learning** knowledge. Previously worked as a manufacturing manager, leading a team of 20 engaged in daily production. Volunteered in Code in Place hosted by Stanford University, delivering online Python lessons to a group of 15 students. An excellent team player with great team management and communications skills.

Email: jkmoo0412@hotmail.com

Mobile: 0892059402

Education

University College Dublin

MSc Computer Science; GPA:3.82

Dublin, Ireland

Sep 2022 – Dec 2023

University College DublinDublin, IrelandBSc Food Science; GPA:3.77Sep 2017 – Jun 2021

Experience

Stanford University
Dublin, Ireland
Section Leader
Apr 2023 – Jun 2023

• Participating in Code in Place, an online introductory coding course

• Conducting weekly lessons for a cohort of 15 students

• Teaching topics including Python, Animations, Console Programming, Graphic Programming etc.

Krispy KremeManufacturing Manager
Sep 2021 – Jun 2022

• Managing a 20-member team for daily production operations

- Ensuring adherence to safety protocols, HACCP principles, and legal regulations
- Maintaining accurate inventory control, yield records, and traceability documents

Projects

Afterparty

an event impact analysis tool which provides insights into how the busyness of urban areas are impacted by large-scale event.

- Utilized React.js, Mapbox GL.js, and Figma for the frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Node.js, Express.js, Flask, and Apache
- Developed prediction models using Random Forest and XGBoost

Dublin Bikes

a web application providing real-time information and journey planning for bike-sharing services.

- Utilized Vanilla JS, HTML, CSS, and Google Maps API for frontend development
- Implemented the backend with Flask, MySQL, AWS EC2, AWS RDS, Gunicorn, Nginx
- Developed prediction models using Linear Regression

Asteroids

a classic arcade video game which player controls a spaceship in an asteroid field to destroy incoming asteroids.

- Developed using Java
- Used JavaFX as the GUI framework

Technical Skills

- Programming languages: Python, JavaScript, Java, Ruby, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, Object-oriented
- Frameworks: React.js, Flask, Express.js, JavaFX, Pygame
- Database: MySOL, AWS RDS
- OS: Linux, Windows
- Tools: VSCode, Jupyter Notebook, Eclipse, GitHub, Microsoft Office, GCP, AWS, WordPress, Apache Maven
- Machine Learning: Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, Random Forest, XGBoost, KNN, Scikit-learn
- Others: Data Structures and Algorithms, Object-Oriented Programming, Networking (TCP/IP), REST API